<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>@thiskurt</title>
    <link>https://thiskurt.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on @thiskurt</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2019. All rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2019 21:00:00 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://thiskurt.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>The Fight</title>
      <link>https://thiskurt.github.io/post/thefight/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2019 21:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thiskurt.github.io/post/thefight/</guid>
      <description>It had been The Kid’s dream ever since he started boxing, his therapist had suggested it as a way to work out his anger, his anger about himself, his situation and the world, it was just supposed to be an outlet, but as soon as he picked up those gloves he had dreamed of a shot at the title.
He never made it far enough to have a chance for that dream to come through.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Never Judge a Cook by His Oven</title>
      <link>https://thiskurt.github.io/post/neverjudgeacookbyhisoven/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Jun 2019 16:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thiskurt.github.io/post/neverjudgeacookbyhisoven/</guid>
      <description>The sister removed her hands from her brother&amp;rsquo;s eyes revealing the old abandoned hospital making him totally freak out in excitement.
&amp;ldquo;You have to be kidding? There&amp;rsquo;s no way you got a table at Leben? There&amp;mdash; there&amp;rsquo;s a waiting list of several months. How did you do it?&amp;rdquo; He asked excitedly.
&amp;ldquo;I got us on the waiting list. There&amp;rsquo;s not much to it really, you just have to wait a bit,&amp;rdquo; she answered.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Picture of Dorian Bae</title>
      <link>https://thiskurt.github.io/post/pictureofdorianbae/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2019 01:40:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thiskurt.github.io/post/pictureofdorianbae/</guid>
      <description>Dorian Bae was the man Sabrina had dreamed of her whole life. No, that&amp;rsquo;s not true. He was more than she had ever dreamed of. He was more handsome. He was kinder.
He was, as her friend had put it, a hunk beyond dreams.
He had a chiseled and strong yet playful face with a smirk that could have saved the titanic, because it would melt anyone and anything.
His body was muscular and defined, but at the same time warm and inviting, with big arms that could wrap around you so tightly you would forget the whole world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Let Sleeping Beauties Lie - Scene 17</title>
      <link>https://thiskurt.github.io/post/lrg-letsleepingbeautieslie-scene-17/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2019 19:45:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thiskurt.github.io/post/lrg-letsleepingbeautieslie-scene-17/</guid>
      <description>A loud cheer went through the town, people were dancing and singing and shouting, out of nowhere a tuba started playing and the fanfare came marching in.
&amp;ldquo;Everybody quiet down,&amp;rdquo; the Commander said anxiously, &amp;ldquo;you&amp;rsquo;re going to wake it up.&amp;rdquo;
&amp;ldquo;Don&amp;rsquo;t worry, Commander, with the spell we managed to put on it this creature won&amp;rsquo;t be waking up any time soon,&amp;rdquo; Milena explained.
&amp;ldquo;Is it kiss proof too?&amp;rdquo; the Commander asked.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Let Sleeping Beauties Lie - Scene 16</title>
      <link>https://thiskurt.github.io/post/lrg-letsleepingbeautieslie-scene-16/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2019 19:20:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thiskurt.github.io/post/lrg-letsleepingbeautieslie-scene-16/</guid>
      <description>The Fairy was speeding through the air. If she didn&amp;rsquo;t end this now the Dragon would kill them all or even worse they&amp;rsquo;d kill the Dragon and any chance of putting the plan back in action would be ruined.
Not wanting to waste any time she crash landed between the Dragon and Guards causing her to waste a lot of time getting her head straight after the impact.
&amp;ldquo;Stop! Don&amp;rsquo;t kill it,&amp;rdquo; she said to the Guards, or possibly to the Dragon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Let Sleeping Beauties Lie - Scene 15</title>
      <link>https://thiskurt.github.io/post/lrg-letsleepingbeautieslie-scene-15/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2019 20:40:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thiskurt.github.io/post/lrg-letsleepingbeautieslie-scene-15/</guid>
      <description>The Dragon faced the Guards who had drawn their weapons and were ready to attack, well, they pretended like they were ready to attack anyway.
The archer looked at the magic wielder and said, &amp;ldquo;guide my arrows, my love.&amp;rdquo; She nodded. He shot arrow after arrow into the air, they didn&amp;rsquo;t fly towards the dragon, instead they landed around it in a circle their points sticking into the ground, encircling the beast entirely.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Let Sleeping Beauties Lie - Scene 14</title>
      <link>https://thiskurt.github.io/post/lrg-letsleepingbeautieslie-scene-14/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2019 21:50:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thiskurt.github.io/post/lrg-letsleepingbeautieslie-scene-14/</guid>
      <description>&amp;lsquo;We can&amp;rsquo;t charge against it, Commander, it&amp;rsquo;ll burn our skin straight off. If only we had someone that didn&amp;rsquo;t need to worry about that,&amp;rsquo; Jerre said.
In unison they all proclaimed: &amp;lsquo;Dr. Bones!&amp;rsquo;
Dr. Bones, the walking skeleton, walked straight through the fire in all his skeletony glory, unharmed.
&amp;lsquo;Hahaha! No longer will I be known as the &amp;lsquo;Skeleton Man&amp;rsquo;, I mean, my name is DR. BONES, why would you even bother with a nickname in the first place?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Let Sleeping Beauties Lie - Scene 13</title>
      <link>https://thiskurt.github.io/post/lrg-letsleepingbeautieslie-scene-13/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2019 19:30:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thiskurt.github.io/post/lrg-letsleepingbeautieslie-scene-13/</guid>
      <description>The Fairy was calmly floating through the air. She passed a flock of birds who all winked at her and said &amp;ldquo;good job, keep it up.&amp;rdquo;
The face of her mother appeared through the clouds and her voice booming from the heavens spoke: &amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;m proud of you honey, you&amp;rsquo;re doing amazing.&amp;rdquo;
In the distance a loot player was strumming an upbeat feel good song from her childhood. The sun shone on her face and a gentle breeze blew through her hair.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Let Sleeping Beauties Lie - Scene 12</title>
      <link>https://thiskurt.github.io/post/lrg-letsleepingbeautieslie-scene-12/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2019 20:05:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thiskurt.github.io/post/lrg-letsleepingbeautieslie-scene-12/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Everybody calm down,&amp;rdquo; the Commander said, &amp;ldquo;We can&amp;rsquo;t panic. Panicking is what gets you killed when faced with a Dragon.&amp;rdquo;
&amp;ldquo;Not being fireproof is what gets you killed when faced with a Dragon,&amp;rdquo; Jerre corrected him, &amp;ldquo;That and not being able to fly.&amp;rdquo;
&amp;ldquo;We just need a plan.&amp;rdquo;
&amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;ve got a plan!&amp;rdquo; Hrodebert said excitedly.
&amp;ldquo;What&amp;rsquo;s your plan?&amp;rdquo; the commander asked.
&amp;ldquo;When the Dragon strikes, we hit it with our swords.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Let Sleeping Beauties Lie - Scene 11</title>
      <link>https://thiskurt.github.io/post/lrg-letsleepingbeautieslie-scene-11/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2019 19:55:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thiskurt.github.io/post/lrg-letsleepingbeautieslie-scene-11/</guid>
      <description>The small purple blob was yelling out in fear and desperately trying to grab on to the Dragon&amp;rsquo;s tail.
Just as she almost had it the Dragon took a nosedive and she lost her grip and the sleeve of dress which was hanging from one of the tail spikes started to rip.
The Dragon spit flames at the ground and used the updraft of the hot air to lift itself up more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Let Sleeping Beauties Lie - Scene 10</title>
      <link>https://thiskurt.github.io/post/lrg-letsleepingbeautieslie-scene-10/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2019 19:30:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thiskurt.github.io/post/lrg-letsleepingbeautieslie-scene-10/</guid>
      <description>After everyone was kissed awake the whole village gathered in the town square and it was all very awkward. Everyone was so quiet you could hear a mouse coughing.
&amp;ldquo;Thanks, I suppose, but who are you?&amp;rdquo; one of the villager asked breaking the silence.
&amp;ldquo;We&amp;rsquo;re the Royal Guards,&amp;rdquo; the Commander explained.
&amp;ldquo;Royal Guards? We don&amp;rsquo;t have a King do we? I thought we had a Duke?&amp;rdquo; Another villager wondered in surprise.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Let Sleeping Beauties Lie - Scene 9</title>
      <link>https://thiskurt.github.io/post/lrg-letsleepingbeautieslie-scene-9/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2019 19:55:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thiskurt.github.io/post/lrg-letsleepingbeautieslie-scene-9/</guid>
      <description>The Fairy had made it to the cave and, if they were as inept as they seemed, hopefully the Guards had left her enough time to undo the binding spell and prevent part two of her plan from waking up.
She slowly made her way through the golden coins, past the shining diamonds and the virgin skeletons. If it wasn&amp;rsquo;t for inflation and the alchemy bubble of the &amp;lsquo;90s she could&amp;rsquo;ve just grabbed the nearest handful and she wouldn&amp;rsquo;t need to bother with the whole plan.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Let Sleeping Beauties Lie - Scene 8</title>
      <link>https://thiskurt.github.io/post/lrg-letsleepingbeautieslie-scene-8/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2019 16:20:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thiskurt.github.io/post/lrg-letsleepingbeautieslie-scene-8/</guid>
      <description>While everyone else was focusing on themselves and wasting time the Commander and the burly Guard were efficiently and orderly getting the job the done.
They would each switch between the tasks of kissing and explaining what the hell they were doing.
&amp;ldquo;The truth is Reinhilde&amp;mdash;&amp;rdquo;
Kiss.
&amp;rdquo;&amp;mdash;I think the Duke send us off on a pointless mission, because he doesn&amp;rsquo;t trust the King and he thinks we&amp;rsquo;re his spies.&amp;rdquo;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Let Sleeping Beauties Lie - Scene 7</title>
      <link>https://thiskurt.github.io/post/lrg-letsleepingbeautieslie-scene-7/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2019 18:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thiskurt.github.io/post/lrg-letsleepingbeautieslie-scene-7/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;I bet kissing an entire village is not what you imagined when you were dreaming of being a knight, was it?&amp;rdquo; Laura asked.
&amp;ldquo;I, well, I mean, it&amp;rsquo;s just, err, you know,&amp;rdquo; Hrodebert went red in the face. After he had stammered his way through through every filler word in the dictionary he managed to pull himself together and replied: &amp;ldquo;Did you dream? I mean, what was your dream growing up?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Let Sleeping Beauties Lie - Scene 6</title>
      <link>https://thiskurt.github.io/post/lrg-letsleepingbeautieslie-scene-6/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2019 18:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thiskurt.github.io/post/lrg-letsleepingbeautieslie-scene-6/</guid>
      <description>What she was afraid of turned out to be true. Some band of idiots was waking up the whole village. That was the biggest flaw in her plan, anyone could walk into town and start waking them up.
If only the fairies had kept the antidote to the sleeping trick to themselves, but that was the trouble with fairies, they were always telling their tales.
She had to stop them, she would just put them under a sleeping spell too and keep the plan going.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Let Sleeping Beauties Lie - Scene 5</title>
      <link>https://thiskurt.github.io/post/lrg-letsleepingbeautieslie-scene-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2019 22:40:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thiskurt.github.io/post/lrg-letsleepingbeautieslie-scene-5/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;A whole town of sleeping beauties. Well,&amp;rdquo; Jerre eyed a woman sleeping on a pile of dirty linen, &amp;ldquo;in a manner of speaking. We&amp;rsquo;ve got quite the job ahead of us.&amp;rdquo;
He eyed the woman again and turned towards Aldric and Milena, &amp;ldquo;I think the Commander intended for me to have more of a supervising position in this task, I am a senior Guard after all. Why don&amp;rsquo;t you start, Aldric?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Let Sleeping Beauties Lie - Scene 4</title>
      <link>https://thiskurt.github.io/post/lrg-letsleepingbeautieslie-scene-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2019 19:40:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thiskurt.github.io/post/lrg-letsleepingbeautieslie-scene-4/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;You just interrupted a lovely Hex-Mex lunch, I hope it&amp;rsquo;s worth it,&amp;rdquo; the Head Godmother said.
&amp;ldquo;I think someone is breaking the sleeping spell.&amp;rdquo;
&amp;ldquo;I knew she shouldn&amp;rsquo;t have used the sleeping trick again, it&amp;rsquo;s outdated. She&amp;rsquo;s always resorting to the same tricks,&amp;rdquo; the Head Godmother&amp;rsquo;s assistant, who had always hated the Fairy, said.
&amp;ldquo;It&amp;rsquo;s not the same trick, it&amp;rsquo;s an entirely different scheme, just because the magic&amp;rsquo;s the same&amp;mdash;&amp;rdquo;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Let Sleeping Beauties Lie - Scene 3</title>
      <link>https://thiskurt.github.io/post/lrg-letsleepingbeautieslie-scene-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2019 22:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thiskurt.github.io/post/lrg-letsleepingbeautieslie-scene-3/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Bob and Laura, you cover the part of town past the bakery,&amp;rdquo; the Commander said, &amp;ldquo;Jerre, you and I&amp;hellip;&amp;rdquo;
&amp;ldquo;Ahem,&amp;rdquo; Reinhilde, the burly, imposing guard who&amp;rsquo;d been standing next to the Commander ahemed. &amp;ldquo;They&amp;rsquo;re at it again,&amp;rdquo; she pointed towards the Dreamy Archer and the Beautiful Magic Wielder who were making out under a tree.
&amp;ldquo;Unbelievable. And they&amp;rsquo;re supposed to be the Guards that are actually capable,&amp;rdquo; the Commander said ignoring the looks the other guards gave him, &amp;ldquo;Reinhilde, can you do something about this?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Let Sleeping Beauties Lie - Scene 2</title>
      <link>https://thiskurt.github.io/post/lrg-letsleepingbeautieslie-scene-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2019 20:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thiskurt.github.io/post/lrg-letsleepingbeautieslie-scene-2/</guid>
      <description>The Fairy sensed her magic spell being broken. Someone in the village had already woken up. The duke couldn&amp;rsquo;t have arrived yet; someone else must have discovered the place. Whoever these fools were they were ruining everything, ruining her only chance to make it into the Fairy Godmothers.
The Fairy Godmothers where neither fairies nor godmothers, they were simply short, stout witches&amp;mdash;all of them; no one dared question their hiring practices&amp;mdash;with a knack for cons wrapped in fairy tale lore.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Let Sleeping Beauties Lie - Scene 1</title>
      <link>https://thiskurt.github.io/post/lrg-letsleepingbeautieslie-scene-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2019 16:01:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thiskurt.github.io/post/lrg-letsleepingbeautieslie-scene-1/</guid>
      <description>“We better start kissing,” the Commander said.
This was not the kind of order you’d expect from a man like Commander Godfried, broad and serious looking with big bushy mutton chops that met up with an equally bushy moustache. He had the big frame and muscles of a knight and the gently expanding belly of a recent retiree.
“What!?” One of the guards, an old friend of the Commander, replied.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Death&#39;s Detective</title>
      <link>https://thiskurt.github.io/post/deathsdetective/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2019 16:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thiskurt.github.io/post/deathsdetective/</guid>
      <description>Synopsis Death and the Devil&amp;rsquo;s Daughter have to investigate a death before it even happens.
Their search brings them from the cozy depts of hell to the seedy underbelly of a local baking club.
Genres Fantasy, Mystery, Humorous, Short Story
Downloads Via Kobo</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://thiskurt.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thiskurt.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>Hugo is a static site engine written in Go.
It makes use of a variety of open source projects including:
 Cobra Viper J Walter Weatherman Cast  Learn more and contribute on GitHub.
Setup Some fun facts about Hugo:
 Built in Go Loosely inspired by Jekyll Primarily developed by spf13 on the train while commuting to and from Manhattan. Coded in Vim using spf13-vim  Have questions or suggestions?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://thiskurt.github.io/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thiskurt.github.io/contact/</guid>
      <description> First Name  Last Name  E-Mail  City  State AL CA IL      Send   </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>