<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on @thiskurt</title>
    <link>https://thiskurt.github.io/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on @thiskurt</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2019 - 2023</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 Feb 2023 23:50:00 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://thiskurt.github.io/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Sainfeld</title>
      <link>https://thiskurt.github.io/post/sainfeld/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Feb 2023 23:50:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thiskurt.github.io/post/sainfeld/</guid>
      <description>I came across a livestream called Nothing Forever1 which is a weird never ending fever dream of a pixelated, AI generated version of Seinfeld. Interestingly enough one of the things I was playing around with on ChatGPT2 myself was Seinfeld scripts as well.
I&amp;rsquo;m not sure what it is, but there is something about Seinfeld that seems to make it a good candidate for chucking at an AI. Maybe it&amp;rsquo;s just a latent memory of the &amp;lsquo;Modern Seinfeld&amp;rsquo; twitter bot of ages ago?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Fiery Tree</title>
      <link>https://thiskurt.github.io/post/thefierytree/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Feb 2022 16:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thiskurt.github.io/post/thefierytree/</guid>
      <description>The Fiery Tree There stood a Tree with branches of Fire at the heart of the World. The Tree illuminated the World as far as its light and heat would reach. Beyond the World there was only the Darkness. In the World there was everything, there was all the beauty and happiness there could ever be. All of Nature was there, the plants, the fields, the mountains, the rivers, the beaches, the desserts and all the animals.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Bureau of Religious Sacrifice</title>
      <link>https://thiskurt.github.io/post/bureauofreligioussacrifice/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jun 2020 22:15:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thiskurt.github.io/post/bureauofreligioussacrifice/</guid>
      <description>Morris had been standing in line for four hours, he never would&amp;rsquo;ve guessed getting a human sacrifice was such a hassle.
The Bureau for Religious Sacrifice was known for being the slowest in the whole Department. This was mostly due to the habit of sacrificing their best workers to a variety of gods in the hope of acquiring their favour so they would bless them by speeding up the process. This had proven to be counterproductive.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>All Hallow&#39;s Eve</title>
      <link>https://thiskurt.github.io/post/allhallowseve/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2019 23:59:59 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thiskurt.github.io/post/allhallowseve/</guid>
      <description>23:58All Hallow&amp;rsquo;s Eve
Chains clattered as they were dragged across the ground by the ghostly and ghastly creature. The gates of hell gave a rusty sigh as they slammed close again.
The girl froze in place. The sight of the ungodly creatures burned its way through her eyes. Unable to process what was happening her brain literally melted. The creature&amp;rsquo;s dark tongue eagerly lapped it up as it came oozing out of her eye sockets.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Fight</title>
      <link>https://thiskurt.github.io/post/thefight/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2019 21:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thiskurt.github.io/post/thefight/</guid>
      <description>It had been The Kid’s dream ever since he started boxing, his therapist had suggested it as a way to work out his anger, his anger about himself, his situation and the world, it was just supposed to be an outlet, but as soon as he picked up those gloves he had dreamed of a shot at the title.
He never made it far enough to have a chance for that dream to come through.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Never Judge a Cook by His Oven</title>
      <link>https://thiskurt.github.io/post/neverjudgeacookbyhisoven/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Jun 2019 16:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thiskurt.github.io/post/neverjudgeacookbyhisoven/</guid>
      <description>The sister removed her hands from her brother&amp;rsquo;s eyes revealing the old abandoned hospital making him totally freak out in excitement.
&amp;ldquo;You have to be kidding? There&amp;rsquo;s no way you got a table at Leben? There&amp;mdash; there&amp;rsquo;s a waiting list of several months. How did you do it?&amp;rdquo; He asked excitedly.
&amp;ldquo;I got us on the waiting list. There&amp;rsquo;s not much to it really, you just have to wait a bit,&amp;rdquo; she answered.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Picture of Dorian Bae</title>
      <link>https://thiskurt.github.io/post/pictureofdorianbae/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2019 01:40:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thiskurt.github.io/post/pictureofdorianbae/</guid>
      <description>Dorian Bae was the man Sabrina had dreamed of her whole life. No, that&amp;rsquo;s not true. He was more than she had ever dreamed of. He was more handsome. He was kinder.
He was, as her friend had put it, a hunk beyond dreams.
He had a chiseled and strong yet playful face with a smirk that could have saved the titanic, because it would melt anyone and anything.
His body was muscular and defined, but at the same time warm and inviting, with big arms that could wrap around you so tightly you would forget the whole world.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
